Guide to the The Review of Contemporary Fiction/Dalkey Archive Press: records, 1980-1990
Department of Special Collections
- Series I: Review of Contemporary Fiction
  - Kerouac / Pinget
    - "Spring 1956: Fran A Life of Jack Bèrouac"-Tan Clark (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - "Literature of the Fifties: Jack Kerouac and the Delicate Balancing Point" - Unknown (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - "All I Got" - Thomas McGonigle (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - "Write in Recollection and Amazement for Yourself"-Chris Challis (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - "Translator's Preface to Pinget' s Someone"-Barbara Wright (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - "Speech Conference at NYU: Sept. 30, Oct. 1, Oct. 2,1982" - Robert Pinget (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - "The Trials of Translating Pinget" - Barbara Wright (Box 12, Folder 26)
    - "Wanes in Graal Flibuste" - Robert M. Henkels (Box 12, Folder 27)
    - "L'Apocrypha: ou la loi nouvelle" - Stephen Bann (Box 12, Folder 28)
    - "Robert Pinget: The End of a Modern Way"-Stephen Bann (Box 12, Folder 29)
    - "Extremeties of Discourses: Walter Pater and Robert Pinget" - Stephen Barin (Box 12, Folder 30)
    - "Pinget and the Voyage to Some/Nowhere"-F.C. St. Aubyn (Box 12, Folder 31)
    - "Pinget 's Passacacilia: Birds Wings Beating the Solid Air" - John O'Brien (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - "Who is Robert Pinget?" - Jean-Loius de Rambures (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - "The Search for Identity in the Work of Robert Pinget" - Anna Otten (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - "The Absences of Monsieur Songe" - John Sturrock (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - "Discovering the Unforseeable: Robert Pinget's Narrative Adventures" - Germaine Baril (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - "Pinget and Friends" - John Fletcher (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - "Robert Pinget: Family Feuds and Others" -Jean-Claude Varielle (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - "Are You Listening? '-Robert Pinget's Insistent Voices" - Gerinaine Baril (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - "Rats, Cats and Bats: Character, Plot and Language in Robert Pinget' s Plays" - Robert Henkels (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - "Structures of Narration in The Inquisitory: Plot Formation or Senseless Ramblings?"-Jean Claude Lieber (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - "Pinget's The Inquisitory: Or Where Were You on the Night of June 12th?" - Jack Byrne (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - "Between Fantoine and Agapa" -George Railard (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - "Authorial personae in Pinget' s fiction: Mahu,Mortin, and Monsieur Songe" - Anthony Cheal Pugh (Box 13, Folder 13)
    - "Speech and Function: Robert Pinget' s 'The Libera Me Domine" - Tony Duvert (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - "Abel and Bela" - Jean Claude Lieber (Box 13, Folder 15)
    - "Deciphering an Alchemical Cipher: Robert Pinget's Paraichimie" - Bettina L. Knapp (Box 13, Folder 16)
    - "Three Lonesque Hours at Paris' Oldest Cafe or The Attribution of a New Literary Prize"-Albert Rosso (Box 13, Folder 17)
    - "Searching for Jack Kerouac"-Arthur Winfield Knight (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - "A New Field': A Note on The Charma Bums"-William Crawford Woods (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - "The Inner Quest of Space: Twenty-Five Years Later"-Albert Huerta (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - "Kerouac: A Reichian Interpretation" - Joy Walsh (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Typist's Copy: cover-p.3 (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Typist's Copy: pp. 4-45 (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Typist's Copy: pp. 46-95 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Typist's Copy: pp. 96-158 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Typist's Copy: pp. 159-207 (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Typist's Copy: pp. 208-251 (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Text Copy: pp. 4-45 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Text Copy: pp. 46-92 (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Text Copy: pp. 93-133 (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Text Copy: pp. 134-180 (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - Text Copy: pp. 181-end (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Cortazar / Hawkes
    - Correspondence: Alazraki - Gault (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence: Greiner - Higgins (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence: Honig - Olivares (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence: Ortega - Zieger (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Interview with Julio Cortazar (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - "Some Aspects of the Short Story" - Julio Cortazar " (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - On the Short Story and Its Environs" -Julio Cortazar (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - "End of the Game: The Early Fictions of Julio Cortazar" - John Ditsky (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - "Morelli on the Threshold" - Julio Ortega (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - "Auto-Peferencial Elements in 'Blow-Up' and 'The Gates of Heaven'" - Genaro J. Perez (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - "Movement and Stasis, Film, and Photo: Temporal Structures in the Recent Fiction of Julio Cortazar" - Lois Parkinson Zamora (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - "Desire, the Author, and the Reader in Cortazar's Narrative" -Sara Castro-Klaren (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - "Julio Cortazar's redhead night: or Notes on ordering the Universe in Prosa del observatorio" -Evelyn Picon Garfield (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - "The Art of Shaman: Julio Cortazar Viewed as a natie American Writer" -Sharon Spencer (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - April in Buenos Aires: Letter Without a Heading to Julio Cortazar" -Luisa Valenzuela (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Hopscotch: The Novel as Pandora's Box" -Carlos Fuentes (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - "Fear/Silent Toys" -Alicia Borinsky (Box 15, Folder 17)
    - "From Bestiary to Glenda: Pushing the Short Sotry to its Utmost Limits" -Jaime Alazraki (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - "Cortazar's Other Texts" -Saul Sosnowski (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - "Life and Art: An Interview with John Hawkes" -Patrick O'Donnell (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - "The Blood Oranges: Cyril's Lyric" -Stanley Fogel (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - "The Oxymoron as Central Trope in the Passion Artist" -Pierre Gault (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - "'It's a Lawless Country': Narrative, Formal and Thematic Coherence in The Beetle Leg" -Alan Heineman (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - "Virginie as Metaphor" -John Kuehl (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - "The Beauties of Language: Notes on The Blood Oranges and The Passion Artist" -Franco La Polla (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - "The Devil and John Hawkes" - Stephen Weisenburger (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - "Self-Consciousness and Death~, Sleep, & the Traveler" - John Banks (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - "'The Pen and The Skin ': Inscription and Cryptography in John Hawke' s Second Skin" -Mare Chenetier (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - "The Rhetoric of Excess in John Hawkes' Travesty" -Christine Laniel (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - "The Blood Oranges" - Review by Gilbert Sorrentino (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - "Viobata~ Bodies: Hawkes' Second Skin" -Johan Thielemans (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - "Who's Cassandra? For That Matter, Who's Gertrude?" -John O'Brien (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - "Bob and Carob and Ted and Alice Out of Season in Ilyria: Sacrei and Profane Love Among the Funeral Cypresses" - Jack Byrne (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - "Postmodernism and Autobiographical Commentary: The Blood Oranges and Virginie" - Heide Ziegler (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - "Garfish, Chili Dogs, and the Human Torch: Memories of Richard Brautigan and San Francisco, 1966" -Keith Abbott (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - "Cortazar' s Secret Weapons" - Victoria Slavaski (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - "Julio Cortaza, lector" (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Communications and Communications: paralysis, Amnesia, Aphasia" -Andre Le Vat (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Text Copy: pp. 1-37 (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - Text Copy: pp. 38-82 (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - Text Copy: pp. 83-126 (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - Text Copy: pp. 127-163 (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - Text Copy: pp. 164-202 (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - Text Copy: pp. 203-246 (Box 16, Folder 22)
  - Burroughs
    - Correspondence: Abbott - Goodman (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence: Grauerholz - Morgan (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence: 0'Brien, Glenn - Zurbrugg (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Creative Reading - William Burroughs (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - "Revenge of the Ice Box - William Burroughs (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Ruski - William Burroughs (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - The Last European Interview - Philippe Mikriammos (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - Burroughs, Grauerholz, and Cities of the Red Night: An Interview with James Grauerholz -Nicholas Zurbrugg (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Departed have left no address': Revelation/Concealment Presence/Absence in Naked Lunch" -Michael Leddy (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - The Gnostic Vision of William S. Burroughs -Gregory Stephenson (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - William Burroughs: A Personal View" - Allan Ansen (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - The Dynamics Deja Vu of William Burroughs -Regina Weinrich (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - The Revelatory Connection: Inspired Poetry and Naked Lunch - Barbara Estrin (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Burrough' s Theater of Illusion: Cities of the Red Night - Steven Shaviro (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Beyond Good and Evil: 'How to' Read Naked Lunch -Robin Lydenberg (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - The Limits of Intertextuality: Barthes, Burroughs Gysin, Culler - Nicholas Zurbrugg (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - The Burroughs Biopathy: William S. Burroughs' Junky and Naked Lunch and Reichian Theory -Allan Johnston (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - Fastest Brains Preserved - Devid Ohle (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - Freedom Through Fantasy in the Recent Novels of William S. Burroughs - Jennie Skerl (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - Burroughs"- Francois Bucher (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - June Dream - Anne Waldman (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - A Burroughs Primer - Jurgen Ploog (Box 17, Folder 22)
    - Burroughs Live - Glenn O'Brien (Box 17, Folder 23)
    - Each Word Taken Clean, Clean, Clean: William Carlos Williams' White Mule and The Great American Novel -James R. Bettinger (Box 17, Folder 24)
    - 49th Slice from St. Patrick's Day, Dublin 1974 -Thomas McGonigle (Box 17, Folder 25)
    - Book Reviews (Box 17, Folder 26)
    - Excerpts from an Interview with Allan Ginsberg: The Creation of Naked Lunch - Jennie Skerl (Box 17, Folder 27)
    - The Authenticity of an Apocryphal Book -Jacqueline Piatier (Box 17, Folder 28)
    - Miscellaneous Burroughs (Box 17, Folder 29)
    - Typist's Copy: pp. 4-39 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Typist's Copy: pp. 40-85 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Typist's Copy: pp. 86-130 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Typist's Copy: pp. 131-183 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Text Copy: cover - p.3 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Text Copy: pp. 4-38 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Text Copy: pp. 41-85 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Text Copy: pp. 86-130 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Text Copy: pp. 131-186 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Goytisolo / Reed
    - Correspondence: Baxnberger - Gimferrer (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence: Goytisolo - Lenz (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence: Lindroth - Oviedo (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence: Perez - Sarduy (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence: Schaeffer - Young (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - An Interview with Juan Goytisolo - Julio Ortega (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - A Cervantine Readii~ of Three Trapped Tigers -Juan Goytisolo (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - Literature Pursued by Politics - Juan Goytisobo (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - Language, Ideal Reality, and Effective Reality -Juan Goytisolo (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - Vicissitudes of Modejarism: Juan Ruiz, Cervantes,Galdos - Juan Goytisolo (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - Goytisolo's The Field of Nijar and La Chanca -Luccarelli (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Selections fran La Chanca - Juan Goytisolo (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Juan Goytisolo or the Novel as Exile -Carbos Fuentas (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Juan Goytisolo's Novel Trilogy: A Reader's Personal Memory - Gonzalo Diaz-Migoyo (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - "Mimesis and Narrative Discourse: Juan Goytisolo's Search for Immediacy - B.A. Gonzalez (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - The Literary Criticism of Juan Goytisolo -Kessel Schwartz (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Fugal Form in Fin De Fiesta (The Party's Over) -Genaro J. Perez (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Deterritorialization - Severo Sarduy (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Fran Don Julian to Makbara: A Possible Orientalist Reading - Juan Goytisolo (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - La Carcil Verbal: Narrative Discourse in Makbara -Bieder (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - The Apocalypse According to Juan Goytisolo -Julian Rios (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Makbara: Juan Goytisobo 's Fictionalized Version of 'Orientalism - Luce Lopez-Baralt (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Marks of Identity: Identity and Discourse -Aline Schumann (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Makbara: The Space of Phantasm - Annie Perrin (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Interview with Ishmaeb Reed (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - The Free-Lance Pallbearers, or: No More Proscenium Arch. - La Polla (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - Old Gods and New Demons-Ishmael Peed and His Fiction - Jerry H. Bryant (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - The Waxing and Waning of Cab CablcMay -W. C. Bairiberger (Box 19, Folder 18)
    - Ishamel Reed's Raven - Joe Weixlmann (Box 19, Folder 19)
    - Heading Thsm Off at the Pass: The Fiction of Ishmael Reed - Peter Nazareth (Box 19, Folder 20)
    - From Krazy Eat to HooDo: Aesthetic Discourse in the Fiction of Isbmael Reed - Lindroth (Box 19, Folder 21)
    - Reality as Art: The Last Deys of Louisiana Red -Geoffrey Green (Box 19, Folder 22)
    - White Men with Three Names... Fran Scat to Scatology - Jack Byrne (Box 19, Folder 23)
    - Ishainel Reed's Mumbo Jumbo: Form of the Mystery -Boccia (Box 19, Folder 24)
    - Problems of the Novel - Juan Goybisolo (Box 19, Folder 25)
    - Typist's Copy: pp. 4-54 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Typist's Copy: pp. 55-103 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Typist's Copy: pp. 104-156 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Typist's Copy: pp. 157-204 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Typist's Copy: pp. 205-244 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Text Copy: front cover - p.3 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Text Copy: pp. 4-54 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Text Copy: pp. 55-103 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Text Copy: pp. 104-156 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Text Copy: pp. 157-204 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Text Copy: pp. 205-end (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Cela
    - Correspondence: Benet - Ilie (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence: Kerrigan - Kronik (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence: Liddy - Ray (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence: Tindall - Wasserman (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - La Mancha in My Heart - Cela (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - The World of the Bullfight.. - Cela (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - Supper with Lola Pacheco - Cela (Box 20, Folder 18)
    - The Latest Word on the Horse Casinaide, 'Almost-Nobody - Cela (Box 20, Folder 19)
    - The Color of Seed - Anthony Kerrigan (Box 20, Folder 20)
    - The Novel as Concept - Cela (Box 20, Folder 21)
    - The Game of the Possible: Francois and Censorship and Techniques of Dissent - Janet Perez (Box 20, Folder 22)
    - I Must Be Talking About Mrs. Caldwell to El Hey Son Armadans - Liddy (Box 20, Folder 23)
    - Cela: Writing about Death - Rato (Box 20, Folder 24)
    - Camillo Jose Cela - Roger D. Tinnell (Box 20, Folder 25)
    - A Stylist, an Institution, a Book: Cela, Censorship and Mazurca Para Doe Muertos - Wasserman (Box 20, Folder 26)
    - Introduction to The Family of Pasual Doarte -Anthony Kerrigan (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Cela and Spanish Marginal Culture -David William Foster (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Trauma and Tenderness in the Novels and Travels of Camibo Jose - Robert Kirsner (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Cela: The Writer's Trade (In Darkness) - Umbral (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Historical cirounistances and Thematic Motifs in San Camilo, 1936 - Janet Perez (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Mazurca Para Dos Muertos Seen Through Its Characters - Rodenas (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Mother Caldwell Writes to Her Dearly Beloved Son.. -Jack Byrne (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Pascual 's Parole - Kronik (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Watercatch': chapter from Banks of the Sea -Kenneth Tindall (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Fictional Infinities - Sorrentino (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Book Reviews (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - The Art of Greenland -Bodil Koalund (Translation by Kenneth Tindall) (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - An Interview: Camilo Jose Cela/Lubos Junk (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Translator's Notes (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Typist' s Copy: front cover - p.43 (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - Typist' s Copy: pp. 44-110 (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - Typist' s Copy: pp. 111-150 (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - Typist' s Copy: pp. 151 - end (Box 21, Folder 18)
    - Proof for front cover (Box 21, Folder 19)
    - Text Copy: pp. 1-43 (Box 21, Folder 20)
    - Text Copy: pp. 44-104 (Box 21, Folder 21)
    - Text Copy: pp. 105-150 (Box 21, Folder 22)
    - Text Copy: pp. 151-177 (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - Simon
    - Correspondence: Andrews - Duytschaever (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence: Fletcher - Silverman (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence: Simon - Varielle (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence: Wright (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence: Interview with Claude Simon: Autobiography, The Novel, Politics - Pugh (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Reflections on the Novel: Claude Simon's Address to the Colloquim on the New Novel, New York University, October 1982 - Claude Simon (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Claude Simon's Answers to Questions Written by Ludovic Janvier - Janvier (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Fiction Word by Word - Claude Simon (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - History and Fiction in Claude Simon's Novels -Roudiez (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - From Drawing, to painting, to text: Claude Simon's Allegory of representation and reading in the prologue to The Georgics - Pugh (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - The Textualization of Time in Conducting Bodies, Trytich and The World About Us -Duffy (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Metaphor and Metonymy in Flann O'Brien's At Swim-Two Birds - Conte (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - A Cumbersome Hero - Lieber (French and Eglish) (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - Simon and Sartre - Duncan (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - The Georgics: The limits of history - Britton (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - The General in The Georgics - Fletcher (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - Claude Simon: The Critical Properties of Painting -Brewer (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - Claude Simon's I/eye - Anna Otten (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - What We Can Learn from an Open Window -Vareille (Box 22, Folder 19)
    - Metaphor and Metonymy in Flann O'Brien' S Swim-Two-Birds - Conte (Box 22, Folder 20)
    - Book Reviews (Box 22, Folder 21)
    - Meaning and Subversion in Claude Simon's Le Vent: Sane Structural Considerations -Duffy (Box 22, Folder 22)
    - The New Novel - Anna Otten and Karbis Racevskis (Box 22, Folder 23)
    - Typist's Copy: pp.4-46 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Typist's copy: pp. 47-89 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Typist's copy: pp. 90-134 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Typist's copy: pp. 135-158 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Text copy: title page p. 46 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Text copy: pp. 47-89 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Text copy: pp.90-134 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Text copy: pp.135-159 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Johnson / Rhys
    - Correspondence: Ames - Figes (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence: Ghose - Marshfield (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence: Murdock - Wilson (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Introduction to Aren't You Rather Young to be Writing Your Memoirs? - B. S. Jchnson (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Another Interruption: from Travelling People -B.S. Johnson (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - Everyone Kniws Somebody Who's Dead - B. S. Johnson (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - "Bryan" -Ghose (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - Telling Life, Telling Death: The Unfortunates -Tredell (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - B.S. Johnson and the British Experimental Tradition: an Introduction - Mackrell (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - The Truth of Lying: Albert Angelo - Tredell (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - B.S. Johnson - Figes (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - The Book as a Metaphor: Artifice and Experiment in the Novelo of B. S. Johnson - Davis (Box 23, Folder 20)
    - B. S. Johnson and the Consolation of Literature D'Eath (Box 23, Folder 21)
    - Albert Angelo or B. S. Johnson' s Paradigm of Truth -Thielemans (Box 23, Folder 22)
    - Artifice and Paradise in B. S. Johnson's Travelling People - C. Kanaganayakam (Box 23, Folder 23)
    - B. S. Johnson's Intransitive Performance -Splendors (Box 23, Folder 24)
    - No Future - Thomas McGonigle (Box 23, Folder 25)
    - Bryan Johnson - A Big Mother Fucker of a Pisces -Kenneth Tindall (Box 23, Folder 26)
    - Sane Thoughts on Jean Rhys's Fiction - Abbott (Box 23, Folder 27)
    - Jean Rhy's 'Tree of Life' - Harris (Box 23, Folder 28)
    - Jean Rhys: The Men in Her Novels. " -Elain Kraf (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Arrangements in Silver and Grey: The Whistlerian Moment in the Short Fiction of Jean Rhys -Lindroth (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Whispers Outside the Room: The Haunted Fiction of Jean Rhys - Lindroth (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Rhys, de Beauvoir and the Woman in Love - Berger (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - The Paradox of Style, Metaphor, and Ritual in Good Mornin, Midnight -Emery (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Jean Rhys's Good Morning. Midnight: The Boulevard of Broken Dreams - Jack Byrne (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Not Counting the Savages - B. S. Johnson (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - The Imagination on Trial - Interview with B.S. Johnson (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Text Copy: pp. 1-41 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Text Copy: pp. 42-92 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Text Copy: pp. 93-127 (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Text Copy: pp. 128-162 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Bukowski / Butor
    - Correspondence: Abbott - Kessler (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence: lambert - Pringle (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence: Roudiez (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence: Sandarg - Weinstein (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - Bukowski's Ham on Rye and the Los Angeles Novel -Fontana (Box 24, Folder 17)
    - "Women: The Siren calls of Boredom - Jimmie Cain (Box 24, Folder 18)
    - Writing the Great American Novel on the PC -Jack Sanders (Box 24, Folder 19)
    - Some Tough Acts to Follow - Keith Abbott (Box 24, Folder 20)
    - Setting Free the Buk - Locklin (Box 24, Folder 21)
    - A Day at the Races: Gambling and Luck in Bukowski's Fiction - Glover (Box 24, Folder 22)
    - Bukowski's War All the Time and Horses Don't Bet on People and Neither Do I - Locklin (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - A Bottle Stain - Thomas McGonigle (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Mirror of Ourselves: Notes on Bukowski's Post Office - Gibralter (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Bukowski's Chinaski: Playing Post Office - Byrne (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - South of No North: Bukowski in Deadly Earnest -Weinstein (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Charles Bukowski and the Avant-Garde - Smith (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Notes on a Dirty Old Man - Kessler (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - On Flaubert's Bouvard and Pecuchet -Butor (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - The Bagatelles of Theleme - Butor (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Smoke Signals - Butor (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - The Raven' s Reminiscences - Michel Butor (French and Enlish) (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Interview with Michel Baton: The Writer as Janus -Otten (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - Baudelaire in Baton's Passing Time -Alastair Duncan (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - The Application and Development of Michel Bator's Collage Principle in Illustrations IV - Inglis (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - "Mbile: America, The Novel - Jean-Claude Montel (French and English) (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - Butor's Room Without a View: The Train Compartment in La Modification -Pringle (Box 25, Folder 16)
    - Baton: The Writer as Don Juan - Waelti-Walters (Box 25, Folder 17)
    - Expanding Fictions: Baton's Intervalle -Barbara Mason (Box 25, Folder 18)
    - "Michel Butor and the Role of Poetry and Prose" -Aubyn (Box 25, Folder 19)
    - Mobile - Metcalf (Box 25, Folder 20)
    - Situating Butor on the Horizon of Contemporary Critical Perspectives - Oppenheim (Box 25, Folder 21)
    - Michel Butor' s Passage de Milan: The Numbers Gains -Knee (Box 25, Folder 22)
    - "Michel Baton: Synthesis or Dilemma? - Vareille (Box 25, Folder 23)
    - Dreaming the 'Baroque Nile': In the Wake of Butor's Aesthetics - Debaisieux (Box 25, Folder 24)
    - "Michel Butor: Between the Crowd and the Hero -Helbo (Box 25, Folder 25)